Guide to the David Jacks Papers, 1845-1960
Department of Special Collections
- CORRESPONDENCE 1867 Jan.-Apr. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 36. Higgins, E[lisha]to DJ, Mar. 21, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 37. Briggs, M.C. to DJ, Mar. 23, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 38. Owen, [J.J.] to DJ, Apr. 1, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 39. Riordan, M. to DJ, Apr. 1, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 40. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Apr. 6, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 41. Soto, J.M. to DJ, Apr. 7, 1867., 2 pp. in Spanish.
  - 42. Higgins, E[lisha]to DJ, Apr. 16, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 43. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Apr. 23, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 44. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Apr. 23, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 45. Chester, A. to DJ, Apr. 27, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 46. Snow, S.P. to DJ, Apr. 30, 1867., 2 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1867 May-Aug. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 1. Chester, A. to DJ, May 3, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 2. Syme, George to DJ, May 7, 1867., 2 pp. authorization.
  - 3. Parker, W.M.R. to DJ, May 9, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 4. Jacks, David to [Mary C. Jacks], May 22, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 5. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, May 24, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 6. Syme, George to DJ, May 27, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 7. Gove, A.J. to DJ, May 28, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 8. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, May 30, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 9. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, May 31, 1867., 1 p.
  - 10. David & Cowell to DJ, Jun. 7, 1867., 1 p.
  - 11. McLean, J[ohn]) T. to DJ, Jun. 7, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 12. Nims, Sarah L. to DJ, Jun. 7, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 13. Jacks, David to Elisha Higgins, Jun. 8, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 14. Johnson, W[illiam] S. to DJ, Jun. 11, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 15. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Jun. 13, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 16. Hunt, E.0. to DJ, Jun. 15, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 17. McElroy, Robert to DJ, Jun. 20, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 18. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Jun. 25, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 19. Davis & Cowell to DJ, Jun. 28, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 20. Phillips, John Burke to DJ, Jun. 28, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 21. Davis & Cowell to DJ, Jul. 6, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 22. Riordan, M. to DJ, Jul. 14, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 23. Phillips, John Burke to DJ, Jul. 16, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 24. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jul. 19, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 25. Pratt, 0.C. to Cornelius Cole, Jul. 29, 1867., 2 pp. with Cole note.
  - 26. McFadden, Cha[rle]s to DJ, Aug. 2, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 27. Goodall & Nelson to DJ, Aug. 6, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 28. McDougall, A.. to DJ, Aug. 9, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 29. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Aug. l0, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 30. Slocum, W.N. to DJ, Aug. 10, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 31. Slocum, W.N. to DJ, Aug. 12, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 32. Slocum, W.N. to DJ, Aug. 14, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 33. Chester, A. to DJ, Aug. 19, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 34. Peckham, R. [P.] to DJ, Aug. 19, 1867., 2 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1867 Sept.-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 1. Black, S.M. to DJ, Sept. 1, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 2. Stuart, James F. to DJ, Sept. 2, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 3. Pinkham, F.W. to [?DJ], Sept. 4, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 4. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Sept. l0, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 5. Hartman, I[saac] to DJ, Sept. 10, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 6. DuBose, W[illia]m to DJ, Sept. 11, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 7. Goodall, Cha[rle]s to DJ, Sept. ll, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 8. Slocum, W.N. to DJ, Sept. 13, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 9. Stuart, James F. to DJ, Sept. 19, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 10. Griffith, G.P. to DJ, Sept. 20, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 11. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Sept. 22, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 12. Huff John, to DJ, Sept. 24, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 13. Gorrell, Robert to DJ, Sept. 24, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 14. Stuart, James F. to DJ, Sept. 26, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 15. Cole, C[ornelius] to DJ, Sept. 30, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 16. Sherwood F[red] B. to DJ, Oct. 7, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 17. Davis & Cowell to DJ, Oct. 8, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 18. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Oct. 10, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 19. Young, Wesley P. to DJ, Oct. 10, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 20. Conway, E. to James F. Stuart, Oct. 12, 1867., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 21. Adams, Alex[ander] to DJ, Oct. 15, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 22. Davis & Cowell, to DJ, Oct. 16, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 23. Dodge, H.C. to DJ, Oct. 17, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 24. Heath, Lucien to DJ, Oct. 17, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 25. Stuart, James F. to DJ, Oct. 18, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 26. Mulligan, H. to DJ, Oct. 18, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 27. Jacks, David to Isaac Hartman, Oct. 21, 1867., 1 P. & cvr.
  - 28. Doss, John R. to DJ, Oct. 26, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 29. Patterson, W[illiam] H. to DJ, Oct. 26, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 30. Young, W[esley] P. to DJ, Nov. 3, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 31. Cassiday [Samuel] to James F. Stuart, Nov. 4, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 32. Prewitt, James L. to DJ, Nov. 5, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 33. Freeman, Ja[me]s E. to DJ, Nov. 6, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 34. Stuart, James F. to DJ, Nov. 6, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 35. Freeman Ja[me]s E. to DJ, Nov. 7, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 36. Kean, Frank to DJ, Nov. 8, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 37. White, John H. to DJ, Nov. 8, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 38. Lowry, W.H. to Flood & O'Brien, Nov. 9, 1867., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 39. White, John H. to DJ, Nov. 8, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 40. Davis & Cowell to DJ, Nov. 21, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 41. Doss, John R. to DJ, Nov. 24, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 42. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Dec. 4, 1867., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 43. Heath, Albert to DJ, Dec. 7, 1867., 6 pp.
  - 44. [Runrd], J. to DJ, Dec. 7, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 45. Cole, C[ornelius] to M.C. Ireland, Dec. 24, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 46. Shubert, W.B. to C[ornelius] Cole, Dec. 26, 1867., 2 pp. with Cole note.
  - 47. Unknown to Unknown, [1867)., 1 p.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1868 Jan.-Mar. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 1. Cassiday, Samuel to DJ, Jan. 6, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 2. Bailey, S.M. to DJ, Jan. 7, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 3. Ramsay, W[illia] F. to DJ, Jan. 9, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 4. Snow, S.P. to DJ, Jan. 10, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 5. Soto, J.M. to DJ, Jan. [l0], 1868., 2 pp.
  - 6. McCulloch, Hugh to C[ornelius] Cole, Jan. 14, 1868., 2 pp. with Cole note.
  - 7. Cole, C[ornelius] to DJ, Jan. 23, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 8. Thomas, E. to DJ, Jan. 25, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 9. Briggs, M.C. to DJ, Jan. 29, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 10. Jacks, David to Unknown, Feb. 1, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 11. Chester, A. to DJ, Feb. 3, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 12. Chester, A. to DJ, Feb. 4, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 13. Lowrey, W.H. to DJ, Feb. 7, 1868., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 14. Toland & Ashton to DJ, Feb. 8, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 15. Sherburne, Edw[ard]R. to DJ, Feb. 9, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 16. Soto, J.M. to DJ, Feb. 22, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 17. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Feb. 24, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 18. Smith, W.N. to DJ, Feb. 28, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 19. Patterson, _____ to DJ, Feb. 29, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 20. Taylor, Alex[ander] S. to DJ, Mar. 1, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 21. Taylor, Alex[ander] S. to DJ, Mar. 1, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 22. Cassiday, Samuel to DJ, Mar. 2, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 23. Smith, W[illia]m N. to DJ, Mar. 4, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 24. Sweeny, J.P. & Co. to DJ, Mar. 6, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 25. Williams & Thornton to DJ, Mar. 7, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 26. Childs, William to DJ, Mar. 10, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 27. Danzkin, G. to [William] Gafney, Mar. 11, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 28. Maclay, to DJ, Mar. 13, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 29. Ashley, [Annie] to DJ, Mar. 14, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 30. McColl, William to DJ, Mar. 14, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 31. Sherwood, Eugene to DJ, Mar. 15, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 32. Blasdel, H.G. to DJ, Mar. 18, 1868., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 33. Patterson, [William H.] to DJ, Mar. 18, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 34. Chester, A. to DJ, Mar. 20, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 35. Sherwood, Eugene to DJ, Mar. 20, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 36. McDougall, J[ames] H. to DJ, Mar. 22, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 37. Reynolds, John to DJ, Mar. 23, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 38. Smith, W(illia]m N. to DJ, Mar. 23, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 39. Ashley, [Annie] to DJ, Mar. 24, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 40. Ashley, [Annie] to DJ, Mar. 25, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 41. Higgins, E[lisha] & Co. to DJ, Mar. 25, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 42. Ashley, [Annie] to DJ, Mar. 27, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 43. McColl, W[illiam] to DJ, Mar. 27, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 44. Cassiday, Samuel to DJ, Mar. 28, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 45. Cassiday, Samuel to DJ, Mar. 30, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 46. Frontin, Joseph to DJ, Mar. 30, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 47. Taylor, Alex[ander] S. to DJ, Mar. 30, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 48. Cassiday, Samuel to DJ, Mar. 31, 1868., 2 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1868 Apr.-Jun. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 1. Cassiday, Samuel to DJ, Apr. 1, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 2. Jacks, David to Samuel Cassiday, Apr. 8, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 3. Taylor, Alex. S. to DJ, Apr. 10, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 4. Peyton, Bernard to [M.] C. Ireland, Apr. 12, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 5. Bennett & Co. and John Taylor & Co. to DJ, Apr. 13, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 6. Davis & Cowell, to DJ, Apr. 15, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 7. Newman, 0. to DJ, Apr. 15, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 8. Hamilton, W(illia]m to DJ, Apr. 16, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 9. Chester, A. to DJ, Apr. 19, 1868., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 10. Romie, C[harles] T. to DJ, Apr. 19, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 11. Ord, James L. to DJ, Apr. 21, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 12. David & Cowell to DJ, Apr. 28, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 13. Taylor, John & Co. to DJ, Apr. 28, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 14. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Apr. 29, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 15. Ord, E[dward] 0.C. to DJ, Apr. 29, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 16. Cassiday, Samuel to DJ, Apr. 30, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 17. Chevers, W.H. to DJ, Apr. 30, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 18. Yoell, J. Alexander to DJ, Apr., 1868., 3 pp.
  - 19. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, May 4, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 20. Ashley, [Annie] to DJ, May 10, 1868., 3 pp
  - 21. Mothersead, A.J. to DJ, May 12, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 22. Rowland Bailey Co. to DJ, May 13, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 23. Spring, John R. to DJ, May 15, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 24. Rowland Bailey Co. to DJ, May 17, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 25. Berwick Edw[ar]d to DJ, May 18, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 26. Newman, C. to DJ, May 19, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 27. Lynch & [Graigg] to DJ, May 27, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 28. Soto, J.M. to DJ, May 27, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 29. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Jun. 2, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 30. Soto, J.M. to DJ, Jun. 5, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 31. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Jun. 6, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 32. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Jun. 9, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 33. Cady, E. Smith to DJ, Jun. 14, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 34. Crosett, J. [F.] to DJ, Jun. 15, 1868., 3 pp. (? J. T.)
  - 35. Reynolds, John K. to DJ, Jun. 15, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 36. Wallace, W.T. to DJ, Jun. 15, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 37. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jun. 16, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 38. Badger & Lindenberger to M.J. Ireland, Jun. 19, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 39. Romie, C[harles] T. to DJ, Jun. 19, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 40. Sweeney, J.P. & Co. to DJ, Jun. 20, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 41. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jun. 23, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 42. Harrison, Ralph C. to DJ, Jun. 24, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 43. Young, J.S. to DJ, Jun. 28, 1868., 2 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1868 Jul.-Sept. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 1. Meily, E.P. to Unknown, Jul. 4, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 2. Sears, R.W. to DJ, Jul. 6, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 3. Cassiday, Samuel to DJ, Jul. 9, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 4. Hawley & Co. to [M.] C. Ireland, Jul. 9, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 5. Griffin, Edward to DJ, Jul. 12, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 6. Murray, John to DJ, Jul. 13, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 7. Edwards, N.B. to [M.C.] Ireland, Jul. 14, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 8. Bailey, S.M. to DJ, Jul. 16, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 9. Williamson, R.S. to DJ, Jul. 18, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 10. Romie, C[harles] T. to DJ, Jul. 28, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 11. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Jul. 24, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 12. Pardee, F.P. to DJ, Jul. 25, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 13. Ford & Sanborn, to M.C. Ireland, Jul. 27, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 14. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Jul. 28, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 15. Riggs, Robert to DJ, Jul. 28, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 16. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Aug. 12, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 17. Morris, James to DJ, Aug. 2, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 18. Griffin, Geo[rge] B. to [?DJ], Aug. 3, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 19. Yoell, J. Alexander to DJ, Aug. 3, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 20. Lyon, J.B. to DJ, Aug. 4, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 21. McFadden, J. to DJ, Aug. 6, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 22. Stuart, James F. to DJ, Aug. 8, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 23. Gurnee, Clinton to DJ, Aug. 10, 1868., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 24. Bancroft, H.H. & Co. to M.C. Ireland, Aug. 12, 1868., 2 pp. per F.P. Stone.
  - 25. Goodall & Nelson to DJ, Aug. 17, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 26. Kregenhagen, Gust to Unknown, Aug. 19, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 27. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Aug. 19, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 28. Rowland Bailey & Co. to DJ, Aug. 19, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 29. McFadden, James to DJ, Aug. 29, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 30. McNaughton, William to DJ, Aug. 29, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 31. Goodall & Nelson to DJ, Aug. 31, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 32. Yoell, J. Alexander to DJ, Aug. 31, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 33. Bennett & Co. to Unknown, Sept. 1, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 34. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Sept. 1, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 35. Taylor, Alex[ander] S. to DJ, Sept. 3, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 36. Spear, D.A. to DJ, Sept. 7, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 37. Williamson, R.S. to DJ, Sept. 9, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 38. Williamson, R.S. to DJ, Sept. 9, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 39. Lowry, W.H. to DJ, Sept. 16, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 40. Taylor, Alex[ander S.] to DJ, Sept. 17, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 41. Sawyer, Thomas to DJ, Sept. 21, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 42. Dowdy, H. to DJ, Sept. 24, 1868., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 43. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Sept. 26, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 44. Young, W[esley] P. to DJ, Sept. 26, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 45. Taylor, [Alexander S.], Sept. 27, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 46. Patterson, Wallace & Stow to DJ, Sept. 28, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 47. Landrum, W[illia]m M. to DJ, Sept. 30, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 48. Geisel, Mrs. [Dorothea] to [Mary C. Jacks], Sept., 1868., 2 pp. in German.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1868 Oct.-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 1. Wilder, J. [H.], to DJ, Oct. 8, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 2. Loomes, A.G. to DJ, Oct. 9, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 3. Sweeney, J.P. & Co. to DJ, Oct. 17, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 4. Hooper, W[illia]m to DJ, Oct. 19, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 5. Davis & Cowell to DJ, Oct. 21, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 6. Parker, W.M.R. to M.C. Ireland, Oct. 29, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 7. Coles, H[enry] to DJ, Nov. 3, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 8. Coles, H[enry] to DJ, Nov. 3, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 9. Sawyer, Thomas to DJ, Nov. 4, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 10. McDougall, J.H. to DJ, Nov. 8, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 11. Romie, Paul [Y.] to DJ, Nov. 8 1868., 2 pp.
  - 12. Gallagher, John to DJ, Nov. 9, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 13. Hale, T. to DJ, Nov. 11, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 14. Hooper, W[illia]m to DJ, Nov. 11, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 15. Ord, James L. to DJ, Nov. 14, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 16. Soto, J.M. to DJ, Nov. 14, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 17. Bennett & Co. to DJ, Nov. 18, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 18. McDougall, James H. to DJ, Nov. 20, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 19. Stow, W.W. to DJ, Nov. 20, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 20. McDougall, James H. to DJ, Nov. 25, 1868.(Jr.), 2 pp.
  - 21. Goodall & Nelson to DJ, Nov. 26, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 22. Cool, P.Y. to DJ, Nov. 27, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 23. Soto, J.M. to DJ, Nov. 29, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 24. McDougall, James H. to DJ, [Dec. 1, 1868]., 2 pp.
  - 25. Hughes, M[ichael] to DJ, Dec. 2, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 26. Chamberlain & Balch to M.C. Ireland, Dec. 5, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 27. Rowland Bailey & Co. to DJ, Dec. 7, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 28. Epperly, H.S. to DJ, Dec. 10, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 29. Sherwood, Eugene to DJ, Dec. 10, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 30. Cassiday, Samuel to DJ, Dec. 11, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 31. Sweeney, J.P. & Co. to DJ, Dec. 11, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 32. Jacks, David to W[illia]m H. Patterson, Dec. 12, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 33. Stuart, James F. to DJ, Dec. 12, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 34. Fairchild, C.H. to DJ, Dec. 13, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 35. Williamson, R.S. to DJ, Dec. 14, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 36. Patterson, W[illia]m H. to DJ, Dec. 15, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 37. Rowland Bailey & Co. to DJ, Dec. 16 1868., 3 pp.
  - 38. Lee, Julius to DJ, Dec. 18, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 39. Riordan, M. to DJ, Dec. 18, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 40. Soto, J.M. to DJ, Dec. 19, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 41. Hughes, M[ichael] to DJ, Dec. 20, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 42. McDougall, J.H. to DJ, Dec. 20, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 43. Lee, Julius to DJ, Dec. 21, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 44. Rowland Bailey & Co. to DJ, Dec. 21, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 45. Goodall & Nelson to DJ, Dec. 22, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 46. Rowland Bailey & Co. to DJ, Dec. 22, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 47. Yoell, J. Alex[ander] to DJ, Dec. 22, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 48. Davenport, J.P. to M.C. Ireland, Dec. 24, 1868., 3 pp.
  - 49. Stuart, James F. to DJ, Dec. 24, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 50. Dow, George to DJ, Dec. 25, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 51. Hughes, M[ichael] to DJ, Dec. 26, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 52. McDougall, J. H. to DJ, Dec. 27, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 53. Jacks, David to James F. Stuart, Dec. 29, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 54. Flint, Tho[ma]s to DJ, L. Little and F. Doud, 1868., 2 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH D.R. ASHLEY 1868 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 1. Ashley, D.R. to DJ, Feb. 21, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 2. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Feb. 22, 1868., 4 pp. & note.
  - 3. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Feb. 26, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 4. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Mar. 13, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 5. Wilson, Jos[eph] S. to D.R. Ashley, Mar. 20, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 6. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, May 14, 1868., 2 pp.
  - 7. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Jul. 7, 1868., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 8. Ashley, D.R. to DJ, Jul. 8, 1868., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 9. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Sept. 14, 1868., 2 pp. note.
  - 10. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Oct. 20, 1868., 4 pp.
  - 11. Watson, Thomas to DJ, Nov. 16, 1868., 3 pp. receipt for D.R. Ashley's taxes, per W.M.R. Parker.
  - 12. Ashley, D.R. to DJ, Nov. 24, 1868., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 13. Ashley, D.R. - two covers.
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH D.R. ASHLEY 1869. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 1. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Jan. 27, 1869., 2 pp.
  - 2. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Feb. 12, 1869., 4 pp.
  - 3. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Feb. 16, 1869., 2 pp.
  - 4. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Mar. 16, 1869., 4 pp.
  - 5. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Mar., 1869., 2 pp.
  - 6. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Jun. 22, 1869., 2 pp. note.
  - 7. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Jul. 29, 1869., 4 pp.
  - 8. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Nov. 28, 1869., 2 pp. receipt.
  - 9. Jacks, David to D.R. Ashley, Dec. 14, 1869., 4 pp.
  - 10. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Dec. 28, 1869., 2 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1869, 1871, 1872, 1875, 1876-1879 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1. Sudden, Rob[er]t to DJ, May 20, 1869., 2 pp.
  - 2. Jacks, David to M.C. Ireland, Nov. 25, 1869., 2 pp.
  - 3. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Feb. 4, 1871., 2 pp.
  - 4. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Mar. 10, 1871., 3 pp.
  - 5. "Squatters League" to DJ, Oct. 4, 1872., 4 pp.
  - 6. Bailey, A.M. to DJ, Nov. 24, 1872., 2 pp.
  - 7. University of the Pacific, Dec. 5, 1872.Auction announcement. Cover stamped Nov. 25., 1 p. ptd.
  - 8. Ross, J.W., postcard announcing Pacific Grove Retreat. Aug. 20, 1875., 2 pp.
  - 9. Jack [sic], Peter to [DJ], Mar. 3, 1876., 4 pp.
  - 9a. [Pomber], J.M. to D.J. Apr. 22, 1876., 2 pp.
  - 9b. Goodall, Nelson & Perkins to D.J. Apr. 26, 27 & 28, 1876.All 4 letters re: Moss Landing. Signed Jones., 2 pp. each.
  - 10. Cowley, E.J. to DJ, Aug. 14, 1876., 2 pp.
  - 11. Porter, D.C. to DJ, Sept. 5, 1876., 2 pp. postcard
  - 11a. Monterey & Salinas Valley RR Co. to D.J. Jan. 18, 1877.Signed John Markley, sec., 2 pp.
  - 11b. Carr, J.D. to D.J. Jan. 22, 1877., 2 pp.
  - 11c. Abbott, C.S. to D.J. Jan. 24, 1877., 4 pp.
  - 11d. [DJ?] to W.J. Hill. Feb. 13, 1878., 2 dfs. 4 pp. each.
  - 12. Unknown to DJ, [Dec. 12, 1879]., 1 p. typed memo.
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH THE HISTORY CO. (H. H. BANCROFT'S) 1888-91 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 1. Jacks, David to History Co., Apr. 19, 1888., 1 p. ptd. subscr.
  - 2. History Co. to DJ, Apr. 21, 1888., 5 pp. ?mimeographed
  - 3. History Co. to DJ, Apr. 21, 1888., 4 pp. incl. 3 ptd info sheets.
  - 4. History Co. to DJ, Apr. 30, 1888., 2 pp.
  - 5. History Co. (Geo. H. Morrison) to DJ, May 12, 1888., 1 p.
  - 6. Jacks, David to History Co., May 22, 1888., 1 p. subscription.
  - 7. History Co. to DJ, May 28, 1888., 1 p.
  - 8. History Co. to DJ, Jan. 28, 1889., 1 p.
  - 9. Webster, Joshua B. to DJ, Oct. 18, 1890.incl copy of Hist. Co. contract and statement of account., 3 pp.
  - 10. Webster, Joshua B. to DJ, Oct. 29, 1890., 1 p. memo
  - 11. Webster, Joshua B. & L.W. Elliott to DJ, Nov. 26, 1890., 1 p. memo.
  - 12. Webster & Elliott to DJ, Dec. 9, 18[90]., 1 p.
  - 13. "Stockton Mail", reprint of article. [1890].
  - 14. "San Francisco Chronicle", reprint of article. Oct. 16, 1890.
  - 15. Freeman, A.C. to DJ, Jul. 24, 1891., 1 p.
  - 16. History Co. (Geo. H. Morrison, Sec.), Aug. 31, 1891., 1 p. resolution.
  - 17. History Co. & DJ, Aug. 31, 1891., 2 pp. agreement
- CORRESPONDENCE 1889-92 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - l. J[ames] L. to J.P. Jones, Nov. 18, 1889., 1 p. & cvr.
  - 2. [Boruck], M.D. to J.C. Franks, Mar. 9, 1889., 1 p.
  - 3. Ingram, Ed[ward] to DJ, Jul. 18, 1890., 2 pp.
  - 4. Jacks, Lee to DJ, Sept. 23, 1891., 2 pp. & clip.
  - 5. Jack [sic], Isabella to DJ, Oct. 16, 1891., 4 pp.
  - 6. Jacks, Lee L. to DJ, Mar. 22, 1892., 1 p. with clip.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1896 Jun. 7-Oct. 1(Letterpress) (Box 2, Folder 32)
- CORRESPONDENCE 1903 and undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 1. Jack, Louisa to [DJ & Mary C. Jacks], [Mar. 2, 1903]., 3 pp. and cover.
  - 2. Hopkins, R.C. to DJ, n.d., 2 pp.
  - 3. Jacks, David to Ernest Romie, n.d., 2 pp.
  - 4. Jack, Isabella to DJ, n.d., 4 pp.
  - 5. McElroy, R[obert] to DJ, n.d., 2 pp.
  - 6. DeGraw, Henry to DJ, n.d., 2 pp.
  - 7. Foundation for Ice Cream, recipe, n.d., 2 pp.
  - 8. Unknown to DJ, n.d., 1 p.
- LEGAL & OFFICIAL DOCUMENTS 1845-1901 & n.d.(Also blank forms) (Box 3, Folder 34-41)
- FINANCIAL PAPERS 1851-April, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 42-50)
- FINANCIAL PAPERS May, 1864-1890 & n.d. (Box 3, Folder 51-52)
- FINANCIAL PAPERS May, 1864-1890 & n.d. (Box 4, Folder 53-63)
- MAPS & PLATS (Box 4, Folder 64)
- MISCELLANEOUS 1859, 1897 & n.d.(Incl. fragments) (Box 4, Folder 65)
- BROADSIDES & CLIPPINGS 1863, 1876, 1886, 1887, 1888 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- CLIPPINGS 1886-1892 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- CLIPPINGS 1898,1902,1903, 190 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- PHOTOSTATS OF CLIPPINGS 1886-1887 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- JACKS, LEE L.-undated school copybook (Box 5, Folder 70)
- BESTOR ARTHUR E. JR.-notes from printed sources & interview (Box 5, Folder 71)
- PHOTOGRAPHS & PRINTS (Box 5, Folder 72)
- ETCHED PLATES FOR PRINTS (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Margaret Jacks et. al. (and Lee, Vida, etc.) - Personal Papers (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - 1. 1895, June 21.Cert. of Education of M.A. Jacks, John Teltow, Boston Girls Latin School to Cornell U.
  - 2. 1927, Dec. 15.ANS Mrs. R.T. Robinson to Lee Jacks. Encloses 5 photos of Arroyo Seco River Protection Work.
  - 3. 1928, Jan. 9.Calif. Appt. & commission of Margaret Jacks to Monterey Peninsula Regional Planning Commission.
  - 4. 1937, Oct. 28.TLS Lou Henry Hoover to Vida Jacks.
  - 5. 1940, Aug. 24.TLS W.G. Hudson to Mrs. A.C. Balch. Descendents of old Monterey families.
  - 6. 1940, Oct. 29.ALS Monterey Civic Club to Lee, Margaret & Vida Jacks. S. Florence M. Hay. Gift of City Park.
  - 7. [1940?].ALS Lee Jacks to Mrs. Florence M. Hay. Draft of reply to above.
  - 8. 1940, Nov. 18.TLS Janet [Jacks) Balch (Mrs. A.C.) to L.M. & V. Jacks. City Park.
  - 9. 1940, Nov. 20.3 mimeo items re: party by Mrs. Balch.
  - 10. 1954, May 27.Margaret A. Jacks to Wells Fargo Bank & Union Trust Co. Copy - power of attorney.
  - 11-44. 1956, Sept.Letters, etc. re: Testimonial Dinner for M.A. Jacks. ALS & TLS
    Mrs. Alden, Marie J. Allaire, Nellie D. Baker, Mary Trimmer Baldwin, Lee E. Bassett, Mrs. Cecil Bassetti, Alfred D. Coons, Juanita Cooper, Bernice Doud (Mrs. John Francis), Newton B. Drury, Flor de Monterey, Harrison Godwin, Isabel Hartigan, Senator & Mrs. William F. Knowland, Walter S. Mansfield, Laura Metz (Mrs. Arthur G.), Native Daughters of the Golden West, Aubrey Neasham, Augustus Pollack, Doris R. Romie (Mrs. F.E.), Gladys L. Romie (Mrs. Karl T.), Helen Russell (Mrs. Henry P.), Pearl Hawkins Schulze, Ed. Tickle, Alice Toulmin, Tulita B. Westfall (speaks of David Jacks), H. Donald Winbigler (2). Drafts of thank you notes by M.A. Jacks, an invitation list & clips.
  - 45. 1962, Feb. 28.Investment Account.
  - 46. 1962, Feb.TLS Isabell H. Jacks to [Margaret) Jacks.
  - 47. & 48. n.d.TLS Maria Antonia Thompson to [Margaret) Jacks & clip. re: Castro Adobe.
- Margaret Jacks et. al. - Business & Legal (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - 1. 1909,Operating expenses (4 mos.) house, stable, garden.
  - 2. 1916,David Jacks Corp. - indebtedness.
  - 3. 1918, Feb. 15.Jack vs. Jacks - testimony & clips.
  - 4. 1919, Oct.Land sale to Stefano Grossi, Deed.
  - 5. 1921, May.Deed to Monterey City Park.
  - 6. 1921, Aug.clip.
  - 7. 1927.Map - Rancho Aguajito - road condemnation